Now that you have trained your first model,
现在你已经训练了你的第一个模型
there is something very important I want to discuss.
有一些非常重要的方面我想讲一下
You might have seen in the assignment that we had a training set,
你可能在作业中看到了 我们有一个训练集、
as well as a validation set, and a test set.
一个验证集和一个测试集
What is that all about?
这些都是干什么用的？
Don't skip that part.
不要跳过那部分
It has to do with measuring how well you're doing
它们用于衡量你训练的模型的性能
without accidentally shooting yourself in the foot, and
但不会让你搬起石头砸自己的脚
it is a lot more subtle then you might initially think.
这比你最初认为的要微妙得多
It's also very important because as we will discover later,
这也非常重要 因为我们稍后会发现
once you know how to measure your performance on a problem,
一旦你知道如何衡量解决方案的表现时
you've already solved half of it.
问题便已经解决了一半
Let me explain why measuring performance is subtle.
我来解释一下为什么衡量模型性能是一件很微妙的事情
Let's go back to our classification task.
我们回到分类任务
You've got a whole lot of images with labels.
你有一堆带有标签的图像
You could say, okay, I'm going to run my classifier on those images, and
你可以用你的分类器对它们进行分类
see how many I got right.
看看有多少是正确分类的
That's my error measure.
这是我错误分类的数量
And then you go out and use your classifier on new images,
然后又对新的图像使用你的分类器
images that you've never seen in the past, and
你之前从未见过的图像
you measure how many you get right, and your performance gets worse.
看看有多少分类正确 会发现效果变差了
The classifier doesn't do as well.
分类器没能很好分类
So what happened?
发生了什么呢？
Well, imagine I construct a classifier that simply compares the new
想象我构建了一个分类器 用于比较新图像
image to any of the other images that I've already seen in my training set,
与训练集中见到过的任何其他图像
and just returns the label.
并返回标签值
By the measure we defined earlier, it's a great classifier.
根据我们之前对这一分类器的定义
It would get 100% accuracy on the training set.
它在训练集上可以达到 100% 的准确度
But as soon as it sees a new image, it's lost.
但只要看到一个新图片 它就不知所措了
It has no idea what to do.
它不知道该怎么做
It's not a great classifier.
所以这个分类器是失败的
The problem is that your classifier has memorized the training set, and
它的问题在于 分类器只是记住了训练集的内容
it fails to generalize to new examples.
却不能泛化到新示例上
It's not just a theoretical problem.
这不仅仅是一个理论问题
Every classifier that you will build will tend to try and
你构建的每个分类器都有试图
memorize the training set.
记住训练集的倾向
And it will usually do that very, very well.
而且通常都会记得很好
Your job though, is to help it generalize to new data instead.
但你的任务就是 帮助它泛化到新数据上
So, how do we measure generalization instead of measuring
那么 我们如何衡量分类器的泛化水平 而不是衡量
how well the classifier memorized the data?
它对数据的记忆程度呢？
The simplest way is to take a small subset of the training set,
最简单的方法是取训练集的一小部分
not use it in training, and measure the error on that test data.
训练时完全不要碰它们 而是作为测试数据 用来测量误差
Problem solved, now your classifier cannot cheat
问题就解决了 因为你的分类器无法再作弊了
because it never sees the test data, so it can't memorize it.
它没有看到过测试数据 也就无法记住它们了
But there is still a problem,
但仍然有一个问题
because training a classifier is usually a process of trial and error.
因为训练分类器通常是一个反复试错的过程
You try a classifier, you measure its performance and
你先试着调了一个分类器 衡量它的性能
then you try another one and you measure again.
然后又试着调了一个 再衡量
And another, and another, you tweak the model, you explore the parameters,
一个又一个 你调整模型 摸索参数
you measure, and finally, you have what you think is the perfect classifier.
测量 最终得到了你认为的完美分类器
And then after all this care you've taken to separate your test data from
在你精心安排下 测试数据始终与训练数据分开
your training data and only measuring your performance on the test data,
确保只在测试数据上测量性能
now you deploy your system in a real production environment.
现在 你将它部署到实战环境中
And you get more data and you score your performance on that new data and
会有更多数据 然后衡量它在新数据上的表现
it doesn't do nearly as well.
但结果差强人意
What can possibly have happened?
原因何在呢？
What happened is that your classifier has seen your test data, indirectly,
那就是你的分类器通过你自己的眼睛间接地
through your own eyes.
看到了测试数据
Every time you made a decision about which classifier to use, which parameter
每次当你决定使用什么分类器 调整哪些参数时
to tune, you actually give information to your classifier about the test set.
你实际上在向分类器透露测试集的信息
Just a tiny bit, but it adds up.
虽然每次只是一点点 但积少成多
So over time, as you run many, and
所以随着时间的推移 当你跑了很多次试验后
many experiments, your test data bleeds into your training data.
你的测试数据便渗透进了训练数据
So what can you do?
那你可以做什么呢？
There are many ways to deal with this.
处理的方式有很多种
I'll give you the simplest one.
我教给大家最简单的一个方法
Take another chunk of you training set and hide it under a rock.
再在训练集中取一部分 将它藏起来
Never look at it until you have made your final decision.
永远不要看它 直到你做出了最终决定
You can use your validation set to measure your actual error, and
你可以使用验证集来衡量实际误差
maybe the validation set will bleed into the training sets.
或许验证集会融入到训练集中
But that's okay because you'll always have this test set
但没关系 你始终可以依靠这个测试集
that you can rely on to actually measure your real performance.
来测量分类器的实际性能